Rogin, Lawrence Interview Master Tapes 5766 OHM
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Lawrence Rogin Interview Master Tapes
1978
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Rogin, Lawrence
5766 OHM
2.44 cubic feet
1 file folder.
Interviews.
Interview recorded on audio cassettes, May 1978.
8929482
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 07, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 02, 2019
Scope and Contents
Interview recorded on audio cassettes, May 1978.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5689 OH: Marge Rachlin Oral History Interview with Lawrence Rogin 5691 OH: Lawrence Rogin Interview on the CSEA-AFSCME Merger 5766 OHT: Lawrence Rogin Interview Transcripts
Rogin, Lawrence, 1909-1988
8929482
- Rogan and Kenneth Fiester (4 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Rogan and Kenneth Fiester (1 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Rogan and Kenneth Fiester (2 of 4) (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Rogan and Kenneth Fiester (3 of 4) (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Rogan Tape (7 of 7) (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Rogan Tape (3 of 7) (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Rogan Tape (1 of 7) (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Rogan Tape (2 of 7) (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Rogan Tape (6 of 7) (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Rogan Tape (4 of 7) (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Rogan Tape (5 of 7) (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Rogan, Lawrence - 5/2/1978 - UC693A/1 (1 of 7) (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Rogan, Lawrence - 5/2/1978 - UC693A/2 (2 of 7) (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Rogan, Lawrence - 5/2/1978 - UC693A/3 (3 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Rogan, Lawrence - 5/2/1978 - UC693A/4 (4 of 7) (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Rogan, Lawrence - 5/2/1978 - UC693A/5 (5 of 7) (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Rogan, Lawrence - 5/2/1978 - UC693A/6 (6 of 7) (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Rogan, Lawrence - 5/2/1978 - UC693A/7 (7 of 7) (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Rogan, Lawrence and Fiester, Kenneth - 5/4/1978 - UC696A/1 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Rogan, Lawrence and Fiester, Kenneth - 5/4/1978 - UC696A/2 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Rogan, Lawrence and Fiester, Kenneth - 5/4/1978 - UC696A/3 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Rogan, Lawrence and Fiester, Kenneth - 5/4/1978 - UC696A/4 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Rogan, Lawrence and Fiester, Kenneth - 5/4/1978 - UC696A/4 (Box 22, Folder 1)